Guide to the John Nolen Jr. papers, 1906-2000 MS2193
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Oversize maps and planning drawings, 1906-2000; 1918-1967; Series 5
  - Oversize folder 5, 1906-1984; Series 5 (Oversize-folder 5)
    Contents of this folder include: (1) Key West Ave. right of way plat MD Rt 28, Treworthy Road to Great Seneca Hwy, Feb. 1984; (2) 1916 S. Street NW, Wash DC existing condition of house, April 7, 1973; (3) Tentative development plan Metro Project Gaithersburg, MD, January 25, 1962; (4) Good Hope Hills and Suitland Parkway Overlook, undated; (5) drawing of Muddy Branch Rd., undated; (6) Transit and Stadia Survey of M.I.T. property Marion, ME, 1918; (7) Traffic capacity in relation to estimated volume and distribution of peak hour traffic north bound on 14th street, July-August 1944; (8) Plot of land of Silas Coleman, Bancroft Mills, ME, July 6, 1906; (9) Plot of compass survey on O. Dowling Farm Whiting, ME, undated; (10) Newton sewer line design; (11) Person per moter vehicle district of columbia and metropolitan VA, 1920-1965; (12) Comparison of motor vehicle registration in suburban VA with daily traffice on Highway Bridge, 1929-1944; (13 and 14) resolutions by staff of National Capital Planning Commission about John Nolen Jr.'s career; and (15) invitation poster that reads "nathaniel a. owings chairman of the president's temporary commission on pennsylvania avenue, requests the honor of your presence at the dedication of the model landscape for pennsylvania avenue, in fron of the presidential building, twelth street and pennsylvania avenue, northwest, on monday november eighteenth, nineteen hundred and sixty-eight, at eleven o'clock. honored guests: mrs. lyndon baines johnson, mayor walter e. washington